Now that we've uploaded our training and validation data to S3,
将训练和验证数据上传到 S3 后
it's time to construct our model.
下面开始构建模型
When we use the word model,
当我们提到“模型”一词时
we should be very careful about what we mean.
应该要知道它的含义
For now, we mean model as understood by SageMaker,
现在模型是指 SageMaker 理解的模型
which is a collection of information including any model artifacts created during
它是一个信息集合 包括在训练过程中创建的所有模型工件
training and additional information describing how the model artifacts should be used.
以及描述应该如何使用模型工件的其他信息
This will make a little more sense as we go through creating our model.
当我们逐步创建模型时 将更容易理解这些话的含义
To remind ourselves how this works in the high-level case,
为了了解高阶步骤
let's take a look at the high level notebook.
我们来看看高阶 notebook
This is the high level notebook,
这是高阶 notebook
and if we scroll down to training and creating the XGBoost model,
向下滚动到 XGBoost 模型的创建和训练部分
what we did was first get the URI to the XGBoost docker container.
首先获取 XGBoost docker 容器的 URI
We then created an estimator object,
然后创建一个 estimator 对象
which included which algorithm to use by means of a link to a container.
需要指定算法 即容器的链接
Some information about the type
还要指定运行算法的
of virtual machine that should be used to run the algorithm,
虚拟机的类型
where to store the output,
输出位置
and then some other information like what role the virtual machine should have,
以及其他信息 例如虚拟机的角色
and some additional session information.
还有其他会话信息
Next, we set algorithms specific hyperparameters.
接下来设置算法超参数
Lastly, we called the fit method
最后调用 fit() 方法
providing a link to the training and validation data sets.
传入训练和验证集的链接
The ultimate goal of these three steps was to create a training job training.
这三步的最终目标是创建一个训练作业
A job essentially does what it sounds like it does.
顾名思义 训练作业的职责是
It runs an algorithm on supervised data to fit
对监督式数据运行算法以拟合模型
a model and then saves the resulting fit model to a file somewhere.
并将生成的拟合模型保存到某个文件中
We will be setting up the training job ourselves in
我们将在低阶 notebook 中手动设置训练作业
the low-level notebook switching back to the low-level notebook.
回到低阶 notebook
In order to create the training job,
为了创建训练作业
we need to specify all of the bits of information in a single large dictionary object.
我们将在一个大型字典对象中指定所有信息
We're gonna call our dictionary object Training params.
将该字典对象称为 training_params
Of course, we're going to need the URI to
当然 还需要指定
the docker container containing the extra boost algorithm.
包含 XGBoost 算法的 docker 容器对应的 URI
Next, we make sure to specify what role
接着指定最终将创建的虚拟机
the virtual machine that we will eventually create should have.
应具备的角色
Next, we need to specify the algorithm we wish to run,
我们需要指定要运行的算法
we do that by specifying a link to the container.
方法是指定容器的链接
Next, we need to specify where the resulting model should be saved.
还需要指定生成的模型的保存位置
This output of our algorithm is what is called the modal artifacts.
这个算法输出称为模型工件
Next, we need to describe
接下来我们需要描述
what properties the virtual machine we are going to run our algorithm on should have.
运行算法所在的虚拟机应该具备的属性
In our case, we are going to use a single virtual machine which is
对我们来说 我们将使用 1 个虚拟机
relatively medium powered and does not require too much in the way of storage.
该虚拟机相对中等强大 我们不需要太多的存储空间
This parameter sets a timeout condition.
这个参数会设置超时条件
Essentially if the training algorithm gets stuck
如果训练算法遇到问题
in some sort of infinite or very long loop,
会无限运行或是很长的循环
this makes sure that our Virtual Machine doesn't run forever.
这个条件可以使虚拟机不会永远运行下去
Those are the parameters that make up the algorithm specification.
这些就是算法规范参数
Now we need to set the parameters that are specific to the algorithm we've chosen,
现在需要指定所选算法特有的参数
in our case X D boost,
我们的算法是 XGBoost
we can do that here.
我们可以在这里指定
As you may notice, the hyperparameters that we've chosen
你可能发现了 我们在这里选择的超参数
here are the same as the ones that appear in the high-level notebook.
与在高阶 notebook 中设置的超参数一样
Next, we need to tell SageMaker where to pull the data from.
接着 我们需要告诉 SageMaker 从何处获取数据
In particular, we need to tell it where the training data is,
我们需要告诉 SageMaker 训练数据在哪
in this case it is in S3,
对我们来说 在 S3 中
and it is CSV data,
属于 CSV 数据
and the validation data,
还要告诉验证数据的位置
which is also on S3 and is also CSV data.
也在 S3 上 也是 CSV 数据
So, now we have specified which hour them to use,
我们已经指定了要使用什么算法
parameters specific to that algorithm,
该算法特定的参数
and the data that is sent to the algorithm.
以及发送给该算法的数据
All that is left is to ask SageMaker to
现在只剩下
construct the training job with the parameters that we have chosen.
让 SageMaker 使用我们选择的参数构建训练作业
One additional parameter that must be included is a name.
还有一个参数必须指定 即名称
Every training job must have a name and that name
每个训练作业都必须有一个名称
must be unique The way that we make sure that
该名称必须是唯一的
our training job has a unique name is by including a timestamp at the end of the name.
设定唯一名称的方法是在名称后面添加时间戳
Once we've done that,
设定好名称后
we asked SageMaker to create the training job and away it goes.
我们要求 SageMaker 创建训练作业 SageMaker 开始创建了
Just like when doing the batch transform,
就像批次转换一样
the training job is being created in
训练作业也在后台创建
the background and once it has been created it will be executed.
创建好后就会执行
If we want to have some sort of visual representation of what is
如果我们想直观地了解发生的情况
going on and to alert us when that training job has completed,
并且想知道何时训练作业运行完毕了
we need to use this logs for job method and include the wait equals true parameter.
我们需要使用这个 logs_for_job 方法并设定 wait=true
Now we just need to wait for our training job to complete.
现在只需等待训练作业运行完毕了